assetworks.com 2017-03-20

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us. AssetWorks LLC ("AssetWorks") is committed to protecting
your privacy and maintaining the integrity of any identifiable information ("Personal
Information") we collect about you. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to outline the steps we
take to keep your Personal Information confidential, to inform you about how and why we
collect Personal Information and to provide you with our contact information in case you have
any questions or concerns arising out of our Privacy Policy.
Protecting your privacy and maintaining the integrity of Personal Information means that: we
will keep your information and the business you do with us in confidence; we will not sell, rent
or loan your information to third parties; we will respect your privacy when we may contact you
concerning various products and services which we make available to you from time to time;
you will have control over how we obtain, use and under circumstances give out information
about you; and you will have access to the information that we have about you.
Why AssetWorks May Collect Personal Information
AssetWorks collects Personal Information and uses it in order to:
     •   Establish identity;
     •   Perform necessary identity and security verifications;
     •   Process transactions and conduct business;
     •   Deliver products and services;
     •   Provide customer support and services;
     •   Provide ongoing service delivery;
     •   Provide you with information;
     •   Improve products, services and service delivery;
     •   Better understand your needs, interests and suitability for various products and services;
     •   Recommend specific products and services that may meet your needs;
     •   Respond to issues, questions, and queries;
     •   Protect you and us against errors or fraud; and
     •   Co-operate with law enforcement and legal authorities, where required, to comply with
         applicable laws and with court orders.
AssetWorks will collect, use and may disclose personal information only for purposes that a
reasonable person would consider appropriate in the circumstances; and endeavors to collect as
little information as possible as may be necessary under the circumstances.
Please note that aggregated statistics and information, where the identity of a specific individual
cannot be identified, is not Personal Information. AssetWorks reserves the right to use
aggregated information in any manner it determines, in its discretion, to be appropriate. Use of
such aggregated information may include, but not be limited to, the preparation of aggregated

user statistics and information summaries to improve efficiencies, more effectively describe our
product and service offerings, and assist in the marketing of our products and services.
Aggregated statistics and information will not contain Personal Information.
What Type of Personal Information AssetWorks May Collect
AssetWorks collects various types of Personal Information. During the course of doing business
or interacting with AssetWorks, or receiving products and services from or through AssetWorks,
you may depending on the nature of the circumstances be asked to provide AssetWorks with:
    •   Geographic (physical) addresses;
    •   Demographic information;
    •   E-mail addresses;
    •   Phone numbers or other contact information;
    •   Names (first, and last or whatever the family identifying name is);
    •   Shipping information;
    •   Billing information;
    •   Transaction history;
    •   Web site usage preferences;
    •   Feedback regarding our business, services, web site and public relations;
    •   Source IP addresses;
    •   Times and dates of access to Web site servers;
    •   Language;
    •   Personal preferences;
    •   Product and service preferences;
    •   Browsers types and configurations; and
    •   Miscellaneous administrative and computer traffic information.
Certain forms of information, such as government issued or private sector issued licenses,
permits, certificates, cards, in the nature of driver's licenses, social insurance/security number,
passports, insurance cards, voucher numbers, and the like, although convenient for identification,
is voluntary. It is up to you whether you want to provide this, or other suitable identification,
subject to any legal requirements.
How Does AssetWorks Collect Personal Information
AssetWorks will only collect Personal Information that you have voluntarily provided to us or
have agreed to have provided to us. AssetWorks will not collect any Personal Information about
you without advising you accordingly (either by way of this Privacy Policy or by way of
providing you with some other form of notice at the time we are requesting or collecting
Personal Information), why and how that Personal Information is being collected and how such
Personal Information will be used or disclosed. AssetWorks may collect Personal Information
through a variety of means:

    •   using our website;
    •   using our services;
    •   in the course of communications with us (face-to-face, by e-mail, by phone, mail or
        otherwise);
    •   in the course of feedback to us regarding our business, services, website and public
        relations;
    •   when registering with us for services or, where relevant, accounts, or, where relevant, for
        the download of our software;
    •   customer, membership, recipient, or service lists that have been lawfully acquired from
        third parties;
    •   through the completion of manual or electronic forms;
    •   website cookies – Cookies are identifiers that can be sent from a website via your
        browser to be placed on your computer's hard drive. You may elect not to accept cookies
        by changing the designated settings on your web browser; however, not utilizing cookies
        may prevent you from using certain functions and features of web site. Information
        collected from the use of cookies is used to improve AssetWorks services;
    •   web beacons – Web beacons are small, graphic images that allows a website operator to
        collect certain information and monitor user activity on its website. A web beacon is a
        very small pixel which is invisible to the user. AssetWorks uses web beacons to collect
        information that is not of a personal nature;
    •   clickstreaming - Clickstreaming is a technology that allows a website operator to track
        the paths that surfers take as they access a website and look at the site's pages, and as they
        use links to other sites. AssetWorks collects such information from visitors to
        www.assetworks.com; and
    •   website traffic information, which is monitored and analyzed in order to determine which
        products, services or features may be of interest to visitors, so we may improve our
        website, products, services, features or other offerings.
In addition, we may review and analyze your use of products and services, to help us serve you
better, and to bring other products and services to your attention, which we feel, will be of
benefit to you. We also collect and analyze information from other sources for the same
purposes.
How AssetWorks May Disclose Personal Information
AssetWorks does not sell any Personal Information it collects to third parties. AssetWorks may
share Personal Information with its affiliates, subsidiaries, employees, contractors and agents in
the course of providing you with our business services, support, or the fulfillment or delivery of
our products or services.
AssetWorks may disclose Personal information if we are required to do so a court of competent
jurisdiction, other legal or regulatory authority, or, if there is a good faith belief, and reliance on
said belief that disclosure is necessary to: comply with any legal process served on AssetWorks;
maintain, uphold or protect AssetWorks' rights or property; protect and ensure the personal

safety of the public or other AssetWorks clients; or protect against criminal or quasi-criminal
activities, or to detect, prevent, investigate allegations of, or address, misrepresentation or fraud.
AssetWorks reserves the right that in the event of a bankruptcy filing, mergers with third parties,
acquisition by third parties, sale of assets (all or partial), or any other transfer of all or
substantially all of AssetWorks relevant assets to a third party, that AssetWorks shall be entitled
share (or sell as an ancillary aspect of the overarching business transaction) the Personal
Information you have provided to us to the third party.
Retention and Disposal
We keep information only for so long as it is needed for the efficient and effective delivery or
fulfillment of the software, products, or services you are using or contemplating using and for a
reasonable time thereafter, or to meet any legal requirements. We will either destroy or remove
information when it is no longer needed.
Security and Storage
AssetWorks endeavors to maintain appropriate physical, procedural and technical security with
respect to its offices and information storage facilities so as to prevent any loss, misuse,
unauthorized access, disclosure, or modification of Personal Information. This also applies to our
disposal or destruction of Personal Information. AssetWorks keeps the Personal Information we
collect from about you strictly confidential. Only authorized personnel have access to this
Personal Information. AssetWorks personnel who have access to Personal Information receive
training regarding privacy protection.
If any employee, contractor or agent of AssetWorks misuses Personal Information, this will be
considered as a serious offense for which disciplinary action may be taken, up to and including
termination of employment or contract for service. If any individual or organization misuses
Personal Information - provided for the purpose of providing services to or for AssetWorks, this
will be considered a serious issue for which action may be taken, up to and including termination
of any agreement between AssetWorks and that individual or organization and possible legal
action against such individual or organization.
Our computer security specialists build security by design by default into our computer systems.
The aim is to protect your information at all times, when it is stored in data files or handled by
our employees. Our systems are also designed to protect your information when it is transmitted,
for example, between our data processing centers, our stores and corporate offices. Personal
Information may be stored or processed in any jurisdiction in which we or our affiliates,
suppliers, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities. By supplying us with Personal Information
you consent to any transfer of this information to other jurisdictions (including countries which
have not been assessed for adequacy of privacy laws).

AssetWorks is and shall continue to use industry-standard technology to maintain the security of
your personal information, and for our connections to the internet; however, AssetWorks cannot
and does not guarantee the privacy, security, authenticity or non-corruption of any information
transmitted through the internet or any for information stored in any third-party system
connected to the internet.
While AssetWorks takes steps to verify that any service providers, suppliers or the like with
whom we share information are committed to maintaining the privacy of Personal Information at
standards that are at least as stringent as our own Privacy Policy and has communicated to them
to refrain from making any independent or unauthorized use of any Personal Information,
AssetWorks does not and cannot guarantee the actions, conduct or standards of any such parties.
AssetWorks shall not be responsible for any claims, damages, costs or losses whatsoever arising
out of or in any way related to third-party connections to or use of the Internet. AssetWorks
cannot and does not ensure the protection of any Personal Information that you provide to a
third-party web site that may reference, be referenced or link to our website. Personal
Information collected by these third parties is not subject to, or governed by, this Privacy Policy.
AssetWorks shall not be responsible for events beyond our direct control. AssetWorks will not
be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, consequential or punitive damages relating to the
uses or releases of Personal Information.
Contact
We are committed to upholding our Privacy Policy. We have policies and procedures in place to
educate and assist our employees and contractors in fulfilling their obligations under our Privacy
Policy. Our policies and procedures will be reviewed on a regular basis and their results of such
review will be presented to AssetWorks' personnel responsible for overseeing privacy matters.
AssetWorks is committed to treating you with the greatest respect and consideration. Please let
us know if you have any questions or concerns and we will take steps to address them. If you
have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, would like to confirm the accuracy of your
personal information, believe that the privacy of your personal information has not been
respected, or would like to update or delete incorrect personal information, please contact
AssetWorks by emailing us at: privacy@assetworks.com or write to us the attention of Privacy
Policy Manager, AssetWorks, 998 Old Eagle School Road, Suite 1215, Wayne, PA 19087. The
Privacy Policy Manager will acknowledge your query and will respond within thirty business
days. If we need to extend timing for response, or have to refuse your request, we will advise
you accordingly, subject to any legal restrictions.
Age
AssetWorks is committed to protecting the safety of children. AssetWorks will not knowingly
request or use Personal Information from children under the age of thirteen without parental
consent. If AssetWorks receives actual knowledge does not knowingly or intentionally collect

any Personal Information from children under the age of thirteen, AssetWorks will take steps to
have such information eliminated. This website is not to be used by anyone under the age of
eighteen. Persons under the age of eighteen are not authorized to use this website and are
directed to immediately discontinue use of this website.
Updates
AssetWorks may from time to time update this Privacy Policy, with the updated policy to be
posted on the AssetWorks website. The use of Personal Information provided to AssetWorks
prior to the update will continue to be governed by the policy in effect at the time the
information was provided. We recommend that you revisit this Privacy Policy from time to time
on a regular basis.
Consent
By using this website, you agree, and do hereby consent, to our collection and use of information
and Personal Information for purposes for which the information/Personal Information was
collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not consent, you are to
immediately discontinue use this website and to refrain from further using this website.
Governing Law and Venue
By visiting and using this website, you acknowledge and agree that the laws of the State of
Delaware shall govern, construe, and apply to this Privacy Policy (without any reference or
regards to any principles of conflict of laws). The venue for the resolution of any question,
dispute, proceeding or other matter arising out of this Privacy Policy shall be the federal or state
courts located in the State of Delaware.
AssetWorks will disclose personal information without your permission when required by law,
or in good faith belief that such action is necessary to investigate or protect against harmful
activities to our company, associates, or property (including this site), or to others.
